// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Circle of Willis is located at the Interpeduncular fossa at the base of the brain",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a branch of the internal carotid artery?",
    answer: "Inferior Thyroid artery",
    options: [
      "Opthalmic artery",
      "Posterior communicating artery",
      "Anterior cerebral artery",
      "Inferior Thyroid artery",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What artery gives off the vertebral arteries?",
    answer: "Subclavian artery",
    options: [
      "Subclavian artery",
      "Common carotid artery",
      "External Carotid artery",
      "Thyrocerival artery",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "Which vertebral level marks the bifurcation of the common carotid artery?",
    answer: "C4",
    options: ["C1", "C6", "C2", "C4"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "The terminal branches of the _______ and _______ arteries all anastomose to form the Circle of Willis",
    answer: "Vertebral and Internal Carotid",
    options: [
      "Vertebral and Internal Carotid",
      "Vertebral and External Carotid",
      "External Carotid and Internal Carotid",
      "Only Internal Carotid",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a branch of the vertebral arteries?",
    answer: "Posterior communicating artery",
    options: [
      "Meningeal branch",
      "Anterior and Posterior spinal arteries",
      "Posterior inferior cerebellar artery",
      "Posterior communicating artery",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a branch of the internal carotid arteries?",
    answer: "Meningeal branch",
    options: [
      "Meningeal branch",
      "Opthalmic artery",
      "Anterior choroidal artery",
      "Anterior cerebral artery",
    ],
  },
  //
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The main paired constituents of the Circle of Willis are?",
    answer:
      "Anterior cerebral, Internal carotid and posterior cerebral arteries",
    options: [
      "Only Anterior cerebral and Internal carotid",
      "Anterior cerebral, Anterior communicating and Internal carotid arteries",
      "Anterior cerebral, Internal carotid and posterior cerebral arteries",
      "Posterior cerebral arteries,Internal carotid and Posterior communicating arteries",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not part of the three cerebral arteries?",
    answer: "Superior",
    options: ["Superior", "Anterior", "Middle", "Posterior"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "The spinal cord is primarily supplied by __ longitudinal arteries",
    answer: "3",
    options: ["2", "5", "3", "4"],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "How many posterior spinal arteries are there?",
    answer: "2",
    options: ["2", "1", "3", "4"],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question:
      "The Anterior cerebral arteries supply the ________ portion of the cerebrum",
    answer: "Anteromedial",
    options: ["Posteriomedial", "Lateral", "Anteromedial", "Medial"],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What cerebral arteries supply the lateral part of the brain?",
    answer: "Middle cerebral arteries",
    options: [
      "Posterior cerebral arteries",
      "Lateral cerebral arteries",
      "Anterior cerebral arteries",
      "Middle cerebral arteries",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What region does the posterior spinal arteries anastomose?",
    answer: "Pia mater",
    options: ["Pia mater", "Dura mater", "Arachnoid mater", "Pons"],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question:
      "The posterior cerebral arteries supply both the medial and lateral parts of the posterior cerebrum",
    answer: "True",
    options: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question:
      "The basilar artery terminates by bifurcating into the ________ cerebral arteries",
    answer: "Posterior",
    options: ["Anterior", "Middle", "Posterior", "Superior"],
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question:
      "The basilar artery arises from the convergence of the two vertebral arteries",
    answer: "True",
    options: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question:
      "What arteries are connected by the posterior communicating artery?",
    answer: "Internal carotid and posterior cerebral arteries",
    options: [
      "Posterior cerebral and anterior cerebral arteries",
      "Internal carotid and posterior cerebral arteries",
      "Ophthalmic and middle cerebral arteries",
      "Basilar and superior cerebellar arteries",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question:
      "What arteries are connected by the anterior communicating artery?",
    answer: "The two anterior cerebral arteries",
    options: [
      "The two anterior cerebral arteries",
      "Internal carotid and anterior cerebral arteries",
      "Anterior and posterior cerebral arteries",
      "Anterior cerebral and Anterior choroidal arteries",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question:
      "Which of the vertebral artery branch supplies the falx cerebelli?",
    answer: "Meningeal branch",
    options: [
      "Meningeal branch",
      "Anterior spinal artery",
      "Posterior spinal artery",
      "Posterior inferior cerebellar artery",
    ],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
